wait wait wait let's do this
but let's get the camera here
is recording
is recording here
and today is day two we go in this bro
ask mauro to take me to the places here that
I probably get to do this talent show
the idea is to find a place that has the cluster of people
where there is also a space for them to present themselves
the boy who was passing by
he spoke old
I will introduce you
the owner of the favela is the boss right
the boss there
different people started to appear
but I was kind of apprehensive that I could
you're taking some risk
wait wait wait let's do this
wait let's get the camera here
a way
exchanging ideas
he was seeing which one is mine too
two balls in hand
close better
strong
there are four
can open
now gained respect
thank god everything worked out
you think it's not good there bro
it's not safe nor old
has
to turn off
the camera
now i will talk to contact here
inside favela and
see if i can do my talent show